LUIS FELIPE ARAÚJO BOTH





CONTACT

luisboth@gmail.com

+55 67 99909 2746

▼ Tiradentes Street, 2096 Ponta Porã

luisfelipeboth.github.io

@luisfelipeboth

in @luis-felipe-both

SKILLS

English Spanish

Programming Python C# .Net **Shell Script** (e.g. bash, sh, ...) **JavaScript** HTML5 CSS3 (Grid, Flexbox, Bootstrap) **RestAPI** Java C. C++ SQL **LaTeX Operating Systems** Windows Linux **MacOS** Software & Tools Visualisation (e.g. matplotlib, mayavi, ...) Data handling/analysis (e.g. numpy, pandas, h5py, ...) **Machine Learning** (e.g. scikitLearn, ...) **GUI Package** (e.g. PyQt5, Windows Forms, ...) Git Jira Scrum Agile **Microsoft Office AutoCAD** MATLAB/Simulink Languages **Portuguese**

ABOUT ME!

Worked as software developer at Fraunhofer IPT in Germany using C# and Python as core programming languages, as well as visualization tools. I'm currently gathering experience integrating agriculture and technology. My main skills are C#, Python, Data handling and Data visualization tools, but not limited!

WORK HISTORY

🛗 04/2024 - Actual

♥ Ponta Porã - Brazil Development of controlled traffic flow with AutoCAD Civil 3D and AgroCAD; Draw of parallel lines for GNSS receivers. **Precision Farming Projects Developer**

🛗 11/2021 - Actual

Ponta Porã - Brazil Farm Manager

Management of seeding and harvesting operations; Administration and control of spraying operations; Project and implementation of season workflow.

10/2019 - 09/2021

Fraunhofer IPT, Student Assistant at Intelligent Aachen - Germany Process Monitoring

HMI programming with Python, C# and .Net;

Machine Learning and Data Analysis;

Software development for communication between CNC machines and CPUs.

1 05/2019 - 09/2019

 P Hexagon Agriculture, Florianópolis - Brazil
Engineering intern on Support and System Analysis

General programming with Python, JavaScript, C++ and Shell Script;

Support on On-board computers; System and Report analysis.

12/2018 - 03/2019

Snowshoe Ski Resort, West Virginia - USA Rental Technician

Summer work and Travel Exchange Program.

6 08/2013 - 12/2015

CAECA - Academic Center of Control and Automation Engineering Volunteer work at college. Vice-Manager of Events

EDUCATION



♥ UFSC - Federal University of Santa Catarina, Florianópolis - Brazil Control and Automation Engineering

12/2012

• MACE School, Ponta Porã - Brazil

High school Graduation

PUBLICATIONS

• Feature selection for predicting milling tool condition by using machine learning methods.

***** CERTIFICATES

- The complete Python Bootcamp from Zero to Hero in Python.
- The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp.
- PROJETOS 123 2.0 Projetos de Agricultura de Precisão.
- Tecgraf Agro Sistematização de Culturas com AgroCAD.

PERSONAL SKILLS

Teamwork	Hor	nest	Punctual	Loyal
Written Cor	mmunication		Verbal Communication	
Motivated	Curious	Willingness to Learn		Self-Learning
Proactive	Dedicated	Flexible	Reliable	